<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Peter Vielehr</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Peter Vielehr</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadtrip-2018</title>
      <link>/post/roadtrip-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/roadtrip-2018/</guid>
      <description>May 2018 road trip through the Southwest and to the Redwoods in California.
We hiked in Kansas, New Mexico, Arizona, Nevada, and California. Follow the link to GaiaGPS to see photos of the trip.
 Gaps on the map are because I forgot to start the GPS Tracker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youth Violence in Nashville</title>
      <link>/post/youth-violence-in-nashville/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/youth-violence-in-nashville/</guid>
      <description>“Violence continues to be clustered in the most impoverished and segregated neighborhoods in Nashville. There were 16,955 violent incidents in the past five years, Three of the 35 council districts in Nashville each had over 1,000 violent incidents. These are districts 2 (1,195), 19 (1,732) and 21 (1,262), which collectively make up North Nashville and account for 25% of the 16,955 incidents”.
 The Nashville Youth Violence Summit Report (p.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Stops in Nashville</title>
      <link>/post/traffic-stops-in-nashville/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/traffic-stops-in-nashville/</guid>
      <description>Hit-rate for Searches Hit rates are an important way to investigate racial bias in search decisions. If a police officer decides to conduct a discretionary search, they make the decision based on their perceived likelihood of finding evidence of a crime. Probable cause searches, in particular, have an evidentiary burden where the officer must meet the reasonable person standard set by the Supreme Court. The officer must have articulable facts and circumstances that a reasonable officer would believe indicates a crime.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>