<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Police on Peter Vielehr</title>
    <link>/tags/police/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Police on Peter Vielehr</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/police/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Officer Delke’s Traffic Stops and Searches</title>
      <link>/post/analysis-of-officer-delke-s-traffic-stops-and-searches/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/analysis-of-officer-delke-s-traffic-stops-and-searches/</guid>
<<<<<<< HEAD
      <description>Click here to download a pdf copy of this report
 All data and code used to generate this report can be found on my Github page
  Officer Delke shot Daniel Hambrick in the back while he was running away on July 26, 2018. He was hired by MNPD on July 1, 2016 and on December 28, 2016 was assigned to the East Precinct. The first traffic stop record for Officer Delke is from March 4, 2017 while assigned to the South Precinct.</description>
=======
      <description>Officer Delke shot Daniel Hambrick in the back while he was running away on July 26, 2018. He was hired by MNPD on July 1, 2016 and on December 28, 2016 was assigned to the East Precinct. The first traffic stop record for Officer Delke is from March 4, 2017 while assigned to the South Precinct. Following his assignment to East Precinct (from December 28, 2016 to February 24, 2017), Officer Delke spent two months in South Precinct (February 25, 2017 to April 20, 2017) before moving to North Precinct and finishing out 2017.</description>
>>>>>>> 5cbff0c4e4980b202db589fe965c44a4769a552f
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youth Violence in Nashville</title>
      <link>/post/youth-violence-in-nashville/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/youth-violence-in-nashville/</guid>
      <description>“Violence continues to be clustered in the most impoverished and segregated neighborhoods in Nashville. There were 16,955 violent incidents in the past five years, Three of the 35 council districts in Nashville each had over 1,000 violent incidents. These are districts 2 (1,195), 19 (1,732) and 21 (1,262), which collectively make up North Nashville and account for 25% of the 16,955 incidents”.
 The Nashville Youth Violence Summit Report (p.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Stops in Nashville</title>
      <link>/post/traffic-stops-in-nashville/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/traffic-stops-in-nashville/</guid>
      <description>Hit-rate for Searches Hit rates are an important way to investigate racial bias in search decisions. If a police officer decides to conduct a discretionary search, they make the decision based on their perceived likelihood of finding evidence of a crime. Probable cause searches, in particular, have an evidentiary burden where the officer must meet the reasonable person standard set by the Supreme Court. The officer must have articulable facts and circumstances that a reasonable officer would believe indicates a crime.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>